{
  "General Facilities": {
    "Carpet/Flooring Issue": [
      { "question": "Location Detail", "answers": ["Interior", "Exterior"] },
      {
        "question": "Carpet Issue Detail",
        "answers": ["Broken", "Loose Floor", "Ripped", "Trip Hazard", "Torn"]
      }
    ],
    "Door/Wall/Window Request": [
      { "question": "Location Detail", "answers": ["Interior", "Exterior"] },
      {
        "question": "Issue Detail",
        "answers": ["Damaged", "Need Feature Added", "Won't Close"]
      }
    ],
    "Electrical Issue": [
      { "question": "Location Detail", "answers": ["Interior", "Exterior"] },
      {
        "question": "Electrical Issue Detail",
        "answers": ["Light Fixture", "Outlet", "Wall Switch"]
      }
    ],
    "Elevator Issue": [
      {
        "question": "Elevator Issue Detail",
        "answers": [
          "Door Malfunction",
          "Light Fixture",
          "Panel Buttons",
          "Other Elevator Issue"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "HVAC Issue": [
      {
        "question": "HVAC Issue Detail",
        "answers": ["Too Cold", "Too Hot", "Bad Smell", "Very Noisy"]
      }
    ],
    "Janitorial Issue": [
      {
        "question": "Missing Supplies?",
        "answers": [
          "Need TP",
          "Need Seat Covers",
          "Need Soap Refilled",
          "Need Towels",
          "Need TO & PT",
          "Need Soap and Towels",
          "No Supplies Needed"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Cleaning Needs",
        "answers": [
          "Dirty Floors",
          "Dirty Walls",
          "Dirty Fixtures",
          "No Cleaning Needed"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "Landscaping Issue": [
      {
        "question": "Landscaping Detail",
        "answers": [
          "Need Grass Cut",
          "Need Weeds Pulled",
          "Need Flower/Pants",
          "Need Grass Cut and Weeds Pulled",
          "Need Weeds Pulled and Flowers/Plants",
          "Need Grass Cut and Flowers/Plants",
          "Other Landscape Issue"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "Misc/Other Fac Request": [],
    "Painting Request": [
      { "question": "Location Detail", "answers": ["Interior", "Exterior"] },
      {
        "question": "Paint Detail",
        "answers": [
          "Halway Wall(s)",
          "Office Wall(s)",
          "Building Wall(s)",
          "Door(s)",
          "Fixtures(s)",
          "Other"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "Parking Lot Issue": [],
    "Pest Issue": [
      {
        "question": "Type of Pest",
        "answers": ["Vermin/Rodent", "Insect", "Other"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Location Detail",
        "answers": [
          "In Walls",
          "Under Floor",
          "In Celling",
          "Inside Windowsill",
          "Outside Window"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "Plumbing Issue": [
      {
        "question": "Is this an Emergency? (Is water exiting?)",
        "answers": ["Yes - Please call 213-4840 immediately.", "No"]
      }
    ],
    "Roof Issue": [
      {
        "question": "Is this and Emergency? (Is water leaking inside the building?)",
        "answers": ["Yes - Please call 213-4840 immediately.", "No"]
      }
    ]
  },
  "Critical Facilities": {
    "Facilities": [
      {
        "question": "What type of request?",
        "answers": [
          "Electrical",
          "Fixture/Equipment",
          "Floors",
          "Grounds",
          "HVAC",
          "Indoor Structure",
          "Outdoor Structure",
          "Plumbing",
          "Roof",
          "Elevators",
          "Fire",
          "Security"
        ]
      },
      { "question": "Is this repair for the jail?", "answers": ["Yes", "No"] }
    ]
  },
  "Road and Bridge": {
    "Dead Animal": [
      {
        "question": "Where is the animal located?",
        "answers": ["In the road", "On the side of the road"]
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the approximate size of the animal?",
        "answers": ["Large", "Small"]
      }
    ],
    "Drainage": [
      {
        "question": "What is the issue?",
        "answers": ["Flooding", "Clogged or Damaged", "Other"]
      },
      {
        "question": "What feature is affected?",
        "answers": [
          "Ditch",
          "Culvert",
          "Roadway",
          "Yard",
          "Pond",
          "Storm Drain",
          "Other"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "Overgrown Vegetation": [
      { "question": "Is this a mowing request?", "answers": ["Yes", "No"] },
      {
        "question": "What feature is affected?",
        "answers": [
          "Ditch",
          "Retention Basin",
          "Roadsides",
          "Sidewalk",
          "Other"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "Road Repair": [
      {
        "question": "What type of repair is needed?",
        "answers": [
          "Pothole",
          "Washboarding",
          "Drop Off",
          "Wash out in road",
          "Depression / Hump in roadway",
          "Driveway",
          "Other"
        ]
      },
      { "question": "Is the road paved?", "answers": ["Yes", "No"] },
      {
        "question": "Please estimate the size of the issue",
        "answers": ["Small", "Medium", "Large"]
      }
    ],
    "Sidewalk / Multi-Use Path": [
      {
        "question": "What is the issue?",
        "answers": [
          "Trip hazard",
          "Cracks",
          "Missing area (Gaps)",
          "Obstruction / Debris on sidewalk",
          "Other"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "Sink Hole": [
      {
        "question": "Have you noticed the issue getting larger?",
        "answers": ["unknown", "Yes", "No"]
      },
      {
        "question": "How does the sink hole appear?",
        "answers": ["Open Hole", "Surface Depression"]
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the approximate size?",
        "answers": ["Small", "Medium", "Large"]
      },
      {
        "question": "What feature is affected?",
        "answers": ["Ditch", "Pond", "Roadway", "Yard", "Other"]
      }
    ],
    "Trash/Debris": [
      {
        "question": "General location of the trash or debris",
        "answers": ["Road", "Drainage", "Roadside", "Other"]
      }
    ],
    "Trees and Limbs": [
      {
        "question": "What is the issue with the tree or limb?",
        "answers": [
          "Tree is fallen",
          "Limbs Hanging / Detached",
          "Tree or Limbs Dead"
        ]
      },
      { "question": "Is it near a power line?", "answers": ["Yes", "No"] },
      { "question": "Are wires down?", "answers": ["Yes", "No"] },
      { "question": "Is it blocking the road?", "answers": ["Yes", "No"] },
      { "question": "Is it blocking the sidewalk?", "answers": ["Yes", "No"] }
    ]
  },
  "Traffic Maintenance": {
    "Sign and Marking Issue": [
      { "question": "What is the problem?", "answers": ["Sign", "Marking"] },
      { "question": "Is it a Stop Sign?", "answers": ["Yes", "No"] },
      {
        "question": "What type of sign?",
        "answers": [
          "Destination",
          "Guide",
          "Information",
          "Object",
          "Regulatory",
          "Route",
          "School",
          "Warning"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "What direction?",
        "answers": ["Northbound", "Southbound", "Westbound", "Eastbound"]
      }
    ]
  }
}
